Everyone has a past. Everyone has a secret.
Young Adam is a drama, thriller, crime film directed by David Mackenzie.
A young drifter working on a river barge disrupts his employers' lives while hiding the
fact that he knows more about a dead woman found in the river than he admits.
Joe Taylor, played by Ewan McGregor.
Ella Gault, played by Tilda Swinton.
Les Gault, played by Peter Mullan.
Cathie Dimly, played by Emily Mortimer.
Jim Gault, played by Jack McElhone.
Gwen, played by Thérèse Bradley.
Young Adam is a 2003 neo-noir erotic drama film written and directed by David Mackenzie and
starring Ewan McGregor, Tilda Swinton, Peter Mullan, Ewan Stewart and Emily Mortimer.
The film is based on the 1954 novel of the same name by Alexander Trocchi.
The film was released in the United Kingdom on 26 September 2003 by Warner Bros.
The film explores themes of dying and death,
adultery, individual, court case, scotland.
The tone is intense and dark and emotional.